Guide to the California Asian American Artists Biographical Survey Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- California Artists Files (non-entry artists), Series 2
  - Naito, Sumako (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Naka, F.S. (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Nakagawa, Denzo (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Nakagawa, Ezo (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Nakagawa, Gus (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Nakagawa, N. (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Nakagawa, Susumu (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Nakamizo, Fuji (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Nakamura, Caroline (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Nakamura, Kazuo (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Nakamura, Kentaro (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Nakamura, Manzo (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Nakamura, Margaret (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Nakamura, Shizuko (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Nakamura, Wakako (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Nakamura, Yoshio C. (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Nakano, C.K. (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Nakano, K. (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Nakano, Kenneth (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Nakano, N. (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Nakashima, J.T. (I.T.?) (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Nakashima, Violet (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Nakata, Chuck (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Nakata, Ichiji (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Nakato, Toshio (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Nakayama, Iarrato (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Nakayama, Masataro (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Nakayama, S. (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Nakazawa, Ken (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Nakomura, Chojiro (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Nao, Senri (Gashimo) (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Naohara, Kay (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Naohara, Kazuo (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Narahara, Masuta (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Naubu, Takeshi (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Ncarai, J.Y. (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Nemiyama, Koichi (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Ng, Ah Too (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Ng, Anna J. (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Ng, Elizabeth (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Ng, Henry (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Nhek, Dim (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Nikaido, Roy (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Nishimoto, Kenneth (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Nishimura, Arthur (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Nishina, Henry (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Nishino, Kichii (William) (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Nishioka, Franki (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Nishioka, Kagu (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Nishiura, Arthur (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Nishiura, Shingo (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Nishiyama, Yae (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Nitta, S. (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Niura, Ichitaro (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Nobori, Bennie (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Noda, Hideo (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Noguchi, K (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Nogura, Hirishi (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Nohira (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Noji, Oliver (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Nojima, Minoru (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Nojima, Mishi (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Nomura, Kenjiro (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Nong, Paul (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Noy, Fong (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Nozaki, Albert (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Numai, Nobunosuke (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Numamoto (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Numata, R. (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Nyagi (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Obata, Haruko (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Obata, Kimio G. (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Obata, Lillian (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Ochi, Ellen Akiko (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Ochi, Tasseki (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Odo, George (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Ogasawara, Kensie K. (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Ogata, Naki (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Ogata, Robert (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Ogata, Yoshi (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Ogawa, Yasugi (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Ogawachi, Kiyoshi (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ohara, Kichiji (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ohta, Hisashi (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Oikawa-Picante, Teri (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Oike, Mako (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Oizumi, Keinosuke (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Ojeda, Arthur E. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Oka, Jane T. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Oka, Mitzi (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Okada, Frank S. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Okada, Koyo (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Okamoto, George (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Okamoto, Hannah (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Okamoto, Henry (Harry) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Okamoto, Kenjiro (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Okamoto, Tom (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Okamura, Nori (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Okawa, Mr. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Okazaki, C. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Oke, Nancy (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Oki, K. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Oki, Yayoi (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Okimoto, Ruth Yoshiko (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Oko, George (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Okubo, Emiko (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Okubo, Michi (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Okubo, R. (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Okuda, Masaye (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Okuda, Woody (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Oki, A.C. (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Okumoto, Aiko (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Omi, Henry (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - On, Lee (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Ong, Koy W. (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Ong, Leroy W. (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Ong, Mira (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Ong, Vincent (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Onouchi, Hisa (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Osaki, Harry A. (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Osaki, K. (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Osaki, M.J. (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Oshiro, Mary (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Osuka, K. (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Ota, Kumezo (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Otsuki, Terumi (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Ow, Samuel (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Ow-Wing, Herbert (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Oyama, Lillie (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Oyema Studio (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Ozaki, M. (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Ozeki, M. (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Pack, Fung Kang (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Padula, Fred (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Park, Eu Chong (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Ping Pong Photo Company (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Pinneo, Jack G. (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Poon, Daniel (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Poon, John (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Poong, Yun Yin (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Poy, Leon (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Poy, Lun (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Pratini, Shi (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Quan, Chuon G. (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Quan, Danny (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Quan, Margaret (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Quan, Sing (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Quan, Susan (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Rey, Chee (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Rianda, Henry J. (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Sada, Ono (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Sai, Jane (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Saito, Frank B. (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Saito, Fred B. (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Saito, Gendo (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Saito, Henry M. (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Saito, Ippachi (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Saito, James Haruju (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Saito, M. (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Saito, Masako (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Saito, S. (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Saito, Siberius (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Saito, T. (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Saito, Ted (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Saito, Timothy (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Saka, Ko (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Sakaguchi, Ben (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Sakai, K. (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Sakakura, R. (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Sakata, Zenkishi (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Sakuma, Loi (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Sakuma, Tai (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Sakurai, S. (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Samura, Shoichi (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Sandona, Matteo (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Sang, Lee (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Sanoye, H. (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Sasake, Yuta (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Sasaki, Hideo (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Sasaki, Joseph D (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Sasaki, Lili Yuri (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Sasaki, Mildred (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Sasaki, Ogado J. (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Sasaki, Sergiro (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Sasano, Lawrence (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Sata, J. T. (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Sata, T.T. (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Sata, Tadanao (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Sato, F.Y. (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Sato, Miss (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Sato, Mitsu (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Sato, Yoriyuki (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Satow, Katsuichi (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Satow, Roy (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Sayano, G.K. (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Sayano, K. (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Sayeda, Oroka (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - See, Eddie (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Seiyen, Hagiwara (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Seki, K. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sekiyama, Hiroko (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Sekiyama, Toshiharu (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Semi, E. H. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Sen, Chih-yuan (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Serisawa, Ikuo (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Serisawa, Yoichi (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Setsuda, Shizuko (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Shibada, Teizo K. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Shigamatsu, Ichitaro (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Shigemitsu, Hamada (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Shigeta, Harry (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Shigetomi, Mary S. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Shimada, Hisashi T. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Shimada, Kainan T. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Shimada, Sekko (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Shimamoto, Gentoku George (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Shimano, Yosh (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Shimanoto, F. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Shimizu, Mitsuzo Mike (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Shimo, Gentaro (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Shimoda, Arthur (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Shimoda, Midori (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Shimohara, Matsubara (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Shimojima, Kaye (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Shimotori, George (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Shimotsusa, Masashi (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Shin, Hank (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Shinabargai, Harry (Bargan) (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Shindo, B. (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Shindo, T. K. (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Shinohara, Mahitaro (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Shinohara, Y. (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Shinohara, Yutaka (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Shirakihara (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Shiroyama, K. (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Shoji, James (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Shonohara, Yutaka (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Shumada, H. (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Sindow, K. (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Sing Sung & Co. (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Sing, Hong (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Sinozaki, S. (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Snow, A.O. (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - So, Edward K. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Sonada, G. (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Song, Chang (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Song, F. Y. (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Song, W.F. (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Sonoda, Kazumi (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Soo, Ah (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Sooy & Company (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Soper, L. (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Soto, Frank (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Souza, Paul M. (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Suen, Kingland L. (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Sugasawara, Hiroshi (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Sugihara, Yuriko (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Sugimoto, Danny (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Sugimoto, Joe E. (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Sugioka, James (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Sukuma, Toi (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Sun Coral Li (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Suto, Harry (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Suyematsu, Kazuye (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Suyemoto, Toyo (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Suzuki, B.T. (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Suzuki, Goro (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Suzuki, J. (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Suzuki, Masakichi (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Suzuki, Sei (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Suzuki, Willie (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Tabata, Jeffrey R. (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Tachino, T. (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Tachumi, Dr. A. (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Tada, Mitsura (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Tade (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Taira, Tsutomu (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Tajiri, George (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Taka, A. (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Takada, Shiro (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Takaha, Chikara (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Takahashi, Dr. H. M. (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Takahashi, Ellen S. (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Takahashi, Henry (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Takahashi, K. (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Takahashi, Martha M. (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Takahashi, Paul (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Takahashi, Roy (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Takahashi, T. (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Takamura, Kango (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Takamura, S. (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Takano, Kioshi (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Takashi, Nanbu (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Takeda, Nisabura (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Takeda, Shiro (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Takehashi, Yama (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Takehisa, Muji (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Takehisa, Umeji (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Takehita, Natsuko (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Takemoto, N. (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Takemura, S. (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Taketa, Takara (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Takimura, Yosukada (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Takishita, S. (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Takuma, Miyoko (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Tam, Edward (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - Tamaka, T. (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Tambara, S. (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Tamura, C. (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Tanabe, Kanako (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Tanaka, B. (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Tanaka, Ianaha K. (or I. K.) (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Tanaka, Isao (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Tanaka, James (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Tanaka, K. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Tanaka, Kelvin S. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Tanaka, Shigera (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Tanaka, T. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Tanaka, Y. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Tang, Frank (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Tang, Howard (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Tani, Jiro (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Tani, Saburo (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Tani, Sada (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Taniguchi, K. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Tasaki, Ernest S. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Tashiro, Yukio (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Tateishi, Shizue (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Tatsuno, Yaeko (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Tera, Aiko (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Terai & Kiro (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Terakawa, Chonen (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Teramoto, T. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Terao, Kakuo (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Terasaki, George (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Terashima, B. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Ting, Lim (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Todashi, Mori (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Toigo, Dan (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Tokita, Kamekichi (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Tokyo Photo Studio (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Tom, Nellie (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Tom, Raymond (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Tomikawa, Yoshimi (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Tomito, Genzo F. (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Tong, David (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Tong, Donald S. (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Tong, Frank (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Tong, Shu Yui (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Tong, Taft L. (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Tonomura, Iris (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Tosha, Katsuji (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Toy, Louie (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Toyama, B. (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Tseu, Rosita (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Tso, Ronald H. (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Tsuchida, William (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Tsugawa, Misako (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Tsuge, P.T. (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Tsuida, Hideko (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Tsukahara, Takuya (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Tsukamoto, Reynum (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Tsukane (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Tsuruda, T. (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Tsuruda, Yoshio (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Tsuruoka, Kakunen (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Tsuruoka, Takutaro (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Uchida, Yoshiko (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Uchigama, H.U. (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Uchima, Ansei (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Uchiyama, Alice (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Ueno, A. (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Ueno, T. (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Ujiiye, Isao (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Umekubo, Masaki (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Ung, Melvin (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Ushikashi, K. (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Usui, T. (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Utsumi, Nellie Jinx (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Utsunomiya, Shizu (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Uyeda, Shigemi (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Uyeno, K. (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Wabika, S.K. (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Wada, Steven (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Wade, Mary Meng (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Wai Cheu Hin (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Wakabayashi, M. (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Wakai, S. (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Wakasa, K. (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Wakasa, Y. (Japanese?) (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Wakida, Takao (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Wall, Su (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Wan, Barney (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Wang, Anne (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Wang, Chang Chieh (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Watanabe, Fumiye (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Watanabe, John (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Watanabe, Kakutaro (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Watanabe, Kay (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Watanabe, Minoru (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Watanabe, N. (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Watanabe, S. (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Watanabe, Satara (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Watanabe, T. (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Watanabe, Yujiro (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Wataru, Shoji (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Weglyn, Michi Nishiura (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Wing, Fong (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Wok, Yloh (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Won, Jack C. (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Won, Quock Chong (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Wong, Carole (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Wong, D. K. (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Wong, Dean (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Wong, Dorothy (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Wong, Edward (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Wong, Ernest (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Wong, Frederick (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Wong, Gail (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Wong, George Y. (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Wong, Gordon (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Wong, Jack (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Wong, Jim P. (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Wong, Joe B. (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - Wong, Kim (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - Wong, Lily Tso (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - Wong, Marijane (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - Wong, Mon L. (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - Wong, Paul J. (Box 10, Folder 117)
  - Wong, S. King (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - Wong, Sam (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - Wong, Siu Ling (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - Wong, Suey B. (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Wong, Suey L. (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - Wong, Suzanne (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Wong, Tan (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Wong, Victor (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Wong, Willy (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Wong, Wilred C. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Wong, Yee (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Wong, Yoko (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Woo, Dear (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Woo, Marie (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Woon, Henry (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Yabuki, Masao (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Yaginuma, R. Munekiyo (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Yama, Shiro (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Yamada, Albert (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Yamada, Katsuaki (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Yamagata, Howard (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Yamagishi, T. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Yamaguchi, C. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Yamaguchi, Tetso (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Yamakawa, Alice (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Yamamoto, Gordon (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Yamamoto, Iwao (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Yamamoto, Koho (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Yamamoto, Lawrence T. (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Yamamoto, Ruby (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Yamamoto, Shinji (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Yamamoto, Taro (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Yamamoto, Thomas (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Yamamura, Jitsuo (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Yamanouchi, Yoshiko (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Yamasaki Company (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Yamasawa, Eiko (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Yamashita, G. (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Yamauchi, Shichisaburo (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Yamauchi, Toru (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Yamauchi, Wakako (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Yamoto, Shogo (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Yan, Lee (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Yanagisawa, Takako (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Yang, John (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Yang, Judith O.W. (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Yano, Kiyo (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Yasaki, T. (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Yashizato, Hiroshi (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Yasuda, I. (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Yasuda, J. (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Yasuhara, Hiroshi (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Yasuhara, M. (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Yato, John (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Yee Wong Studio (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Yee, C.C. (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Yee, Chiang (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Yee, Don (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Yee, Frank B. (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Yee, Jack (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Yee, John G. (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Yee, Judith M. (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Yee, June (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Yee, Kwock (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Yee, Wy (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Yeshimiki, Kima (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Yip, Shair (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Yokoi, George (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Yokoi, Rita S. (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Yokoi, Teruko (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Yokoyama, William K. (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Yoneda, Yosaku (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Yori, Polly (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Yoshi, J.S. (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Yoshi, S. (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Yoshida, Florence (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Yoshida, Kirniteru T. (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Yoshida, Kozo (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Yoshida, Toshio (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Yoshido, Sei (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Yoshiga (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Yoshiharu, H. (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Yoshimeki, Kyo (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Yoshimura, Edward S. (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Yoshimura, Keiko (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Yoshimura, Michio (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Yoshimura, Wendy (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Yoshinaga, Henry (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Yoshinaga, Johnny (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Yoshioka, F. (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Yoshioka, Yoshio (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Yoshioko, Sunjoo (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Yoshita, Jii (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Yoshitazo, H. (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Yoshito (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Yoshiwara, Miss Itsuko (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Yoshizumi, Harry (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Yoshizumi, Haruki (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Yosi, X. (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Young Brothers (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Young, C. Jac (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Young, Jacob Chun Kwok (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Yu, Mr. C.C. (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Yuen, Cahoone (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Yuen, Don (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Yuen, Geri (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Ywe, Jack (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Zaima, Paul (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - Zshiguiro, N. (Box 11, Folder 104)
- Non-California Artists Files, Series 3
  Files on 91 artists not active in California for a significant portion of their career. Contents of files predominantly are photocopies of secondary biographical source materials, photocopies of newspaper articles, photocopied materials from other institutions, and spreadsheets or other compiled documents produced by project researchers, with related and original source materials found in series 4.
  - Hawaii-General (Box 1, Folder 1)
    List of pre-1960 artists active in Hawaii from the State Foundation of Culture and the Arts.
  - Washington-General (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Two brochures of work by contemporary Pacific Northwest artists.
  - Akaji, Bumpei (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Active in Hawaii; resume; SFAA exhibition information.
  - Amemiya, Yosei (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Active in New York; documentation of participation in "Exhibition by Japanese Artists in New York" at the ACA Gallery, NY, 1936.
  - Amino, Leo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Active in New York; photocopies of biographical sources; photocopy of exhibition brochure "Half Century of Japanese Artists in New York, 1910-1950," 1977.
  - Aoki, Yosei (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bhavsar, Natvar (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Active in New York; photocopies of biographical sources.
  - Chen, Bong Wai (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Active in Washington; photocopy of biographical source.
  - Chiang, Yee (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Active in New York. Article on artist's Cold War era travels, writings, and art production.
  - Chong, Fay (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Active in Washington; photocopied information from book "They Painted From Their Hearts"; Oakland Museum of California collection list.
  - Doi, Isami (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Active in Hawaii; copies of letters, resume and other materials photocopied from Archives of American art microfilm; photocopy of exhibition brochure "Exhibition by Japanese Artists in New York" at the ACA Gallery, NY, 1936; other exhibition info and articles.
  - Foujita, Tsugouhara (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Active primarily Paris and Japan; LA Times Index citation; FAMSF exhibition information; examples of artwork.
  - Foujita, Tsugouhara (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Active in Paris and Japan; newspaper articles; photocopies from books.
  - Fujii, Kikuye (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Active in New York; photocopy of brochure from "Exhibition by Japanese Artists in New York" at The Art Center, NY, 1927.
  - Furukawa, Akira (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Photographer active in Hawaii; information from Dennis Reed's book "Japanese Photography in America."
  - Furuya, Kiuzo (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Active in Oregon; photocopies of Museum Art School, Portland, enrollment records; information from book "Oregon Painters."
  - Gado, T.K. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Active in New York; documentation of participation in "First Exhibition of Paintings and Sculpture by the Japanese Artists of New York City" at The Civic Club, NY, 1922; example of artwork.
  - Goo, Ben (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Active in Arizona; examples of artwork.
  - Hamachi, Seimatsu (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Active in New York; documenation of participation in "Exhibition by Japanese Artists in New York" at The Art Center, NY, 1927.
  - Hamada, Shoji (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Ceramic artist active in Japan, visits United States for extended periods; copies of articles and excerpts from books; records of objects in Mills College gallery collection.
  - Hiramoto, Masaji (Box 1, Folder 21)